healthybeautyaid.com 2019-03-01

# Privacy Policy | Healthy Beauty Aid

Your privacy is critically important to us. We, Health Beauty Aid are always promised to give the maximum priority of our reader’s personal information. Our privacy policy page will provide you an outline that describes everything about our privacy policy. Before visiting, please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of what information is being collected about you, how that information is being used, how do we protect your personal information and how to contact us if you have additional questions or concerns.  
What Type of Personal Information Do We Collect?

When you browse our site, we don’t necessarily to need any kind of personal information from your end. But, we need to collect certain basic information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address location or other details to help you with your experience.  
Do We Sell or Trade Your Personal Information?

No, we do not trade, sell or distribute any of the personal information provided by you to others that may bother you.  
Do We Use Collected Cookies and Beacons?

To personalize our visitor experience, to improve our website and to maintain responsible customer relation we use cookies and beacons to store information about our visitor’s preferences, store their specific information on which pages they actually visit, and other information that the visitor sends through the particular browser.  
We use Third-Party Ads on Our Website.

We also visualize third party advertisements on HealthBeautyAid.com to support our site. These third-party ad exchange providers may use web beacons and cookies to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. If you click on an advertisement on our site and visit a site maintained by one of our advertisers, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.  
Deleting or Modification

We reserve the right to alter, add to, delete, modify or change any content or privacy policy from time to time with or without notice.  
Contacting Us

If you still have anything in your mind, please feel free to contact us. We will take care any kind of your tips, suggestions, and complaints to develop our blog.

NOTE: Information published on our website, is only for education purposes. This site does not provide medical advice. Consult with your doctor before using any of these tips or treatments. By using our Site you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. You should access our privacy policy regularly to ensure you understand our current policies.
